this is a quick video to talk about
something I found out it's very esoteric
and as far as I know it's not documented
and go this should be short but pay
attention here we have a lot of people
may not know this but but you can
actually have two different files that
get one gets compiled for a particular
Target operating system type or
architecture this is a go thing I'm not
going to get into the details of that
deeply but there's something very
special that I found out and that is
that the first one the first
alphabetically wins that's the takeaway
so what I mean by that is this if you go
into is other you can put this this
thing at the top here it says any other
operating system that's not Windows
right and here is the function there is
no documentation for that function and
then we open another one that has the
same function down here at the bottom
that has documentation but when I do the
docs you can see go do all you see
there's no documentation the reason for
that is because by the order that that
is is what matters and we've confirmed
this with godoc online as well so it
doesn't find it no matter what but if I
take that same documentation and I put
it um so is it four lines of
documentation right four and I put that
documentation in the alphabetically
first one uh it will be documented
properly so the same God do-- all
command will actually show it up the
moral of the story is make sure that
your documentation for the functions is
either the same in both places which is
super hard to keep synchronized or that
it is in the first one that wins
alphabetically so if you change the
names make sure you move the
documentation sort of annoying but make
sure you do it otherwise your stuff will
not be documented if you document both
separately like this one just does this
because it's this that will be the final
documentation for that function for both
and all operating systems so an
architecture so make sure that you don't
do that which is that's probably easy
mistake to make